Finding Aid for the John J. Bonica Papers Biomed.0118
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence
  - Chronological
    - Jan 1981 - Mar 1981 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Apr 1981 - May 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Jun 1981 - Jul 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Aug 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Sep 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Oct 1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Nov 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Dec 1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Jan 1982 - Feb 1982 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Mar 1982 - Apr 1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - May 1982 - Jun 1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Jul 1982 - Sep 1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Oct 1982 - Dec 1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Jan 1983 - Mar 1983 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Apr 1983 - Jun 1983 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Jul 1983 - Sep 1983 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Oct 1983 - Dec 1983 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Jan 1984 - Mar 1984 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Apr 1984 - Jun 1984 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Jul 1984 - Sep 1984 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Oct 1984 - Dec 1984 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Jan 1985 - Mar 1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Apr 1985 - May 1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Jun 1985 - Aug 1985 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Dec 1974 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Sep 1985 - Dec 1985 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Jan 1986 - Apr 1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - May 1986 - Aug 1986 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Sep 1986 - Dec 1986 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Jan 1987 - Apr 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - May 1987 - Sep 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Oct 1987 - Dec 1987 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Jan 1988 - Jun 1988 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Jul 1988 - Dec 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Jan 1989 - Jun 1989 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Jul 1989 - Dec 1989 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Jan 1990 - May 1990 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Jun 1990 - Dec 1990 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Jan 1991 - Jun 1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Jul 1991 - Dec 1991 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Jan 1992 - Jun 1992 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Jul 1992 - Dec 1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Jan 1993 - Apr 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - May 1993 - Jul 1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Aug 1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Sep 1993 - Dec 1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Jan 1994 - Aug 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - unspecified (Box Unknown container 1490 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
    - unspecified (Box Unknown container 1491 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - Correspondence Logs
    - Mail Log, 08 Jan 1987 - 27 Mar 1992. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Mail Log, 26 Mar 1984 - 07 Jan 1987. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Mail Log, 09 Dec 1982 - 23 Mar 1984. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Mail Log, 06 Oct 1981 - 09 Dec 1982. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Mail Log, 29 Dec 1980 - 06 Oct 1981. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Mail Log, 27 Dec 1979 - 22 Dec 1980. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Mail Log, 01 Jul 1977 - 31 Dec 1977. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Mail Log, 01 Jan 1977 - 30 Jun 1977. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Mail Log, 01 Aug 1976 - 31 Dec 1976. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Mail Log, 01 Jan 1976 - 31 Jul 1976. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Mail Log, 01 Jan 1975 - 31 Dec 1975. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Mail Log, 17 Apr 1974 - 31 Dec 1974. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Telephone Messages, 02 Jan 1985 - 12 Apr 1988. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Telephone Messages, 03 Jan 1983 - 28 Dec 1984. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Telephone Messages, 31 Dec 1981 - 29 Dec 1982. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Telephone Messages, 30 Apr 1979 - 30 Dec 1981. (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Subject
    - Foreign, Jul 1984 - Dec 1989. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Foreign, Jan 1990 - Sep 1992. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - General, Sep 1956 - Apr 1957. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - General, Mar 1973 - Dec 1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Incoming, Feb 1992 - Aug 1994. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Incoming, Feb 1994 - Jun 1994. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Personal, Jan 1958 - Dec 1958. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Personal, Jan 1959 - Dec 1959. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Personal, Jan 1960 - Dec 1960. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Personal, Jan 1969 - Dec 1973. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Personal, Jan 1974 - Dec 1975. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Personal, Jan 1976 - Aug 1977. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Personal, Mar 1978 - Nov 1980. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Personal, Jan 1981 - Oct 1982. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Personal, Jan 1983 - Nov 1984. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Personal, Jan 1985 - Dec 1988. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Personal, Jun 1989 - Sep 1992. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Personal--Foreign, Jan 1974 - Dec 1975. (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Personal--Foreign, Jan 1976 - Aug 1977. (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Personal--Foreign, May 1978 - Jun 1981. (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Posthumous, Aug 1994 - Jul 1996. (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Posthumous, May 1995 - Aug 1995. (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Professional, Jan 1959 - Dec 1959. (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Professional, Jan 1960 - Dec 1960. (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Social, Aug 1954 - Dec 1957. (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Conferences and Travel
  - Miscellaneous Meetings (20 Oct 1947 - 23 Jan 1958: Seattle, WA; Others). (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hawaii Trip (03 Dec 1953 - 12 Nov 1953: Honolulu, HI). (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - European Trip (30 Apr 1954 - 01 Aug 1954: England, France, Italy, Switzerland, Austria, Germany, Scandanavia). (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - South American Trip (16 Sep 1955 - 03 Nov 1955: Cuba, Haiti, Puerto Rico, Venezuela, Brazil, Uruguay, Panama, Argentina). (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Argentina Trip (16 Sep 1955 - 03 Nov 1955: Cuba, Haiti, Puerto Rico, Venezuela, Brazil, Uruguay, Panama, Argentina). (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Postgraduate Assembly in Anesthesiology (9th: 07 Dec 1955 - 10 Dec 1955: New York, NY). (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Postgraduate Medical Study: Anesthesiology. Meeting (16 Apr 1956 - 18 Apr 1956: Kansas City, KS). (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - International Research Society. Congress (31st: 01 Apr 1957 - 04 Apr 1957: Phoenix, AZ). (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Western Conference on Anesthesiology (08 Apr 1957 - 10 Apr 1957: Sun Valley, ID). (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - University of California, Los Angeles Postgraduate Course (27 Aug 1958: Los Angeles, CA). (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Academy of Anesthesiology. Meeting (16 Oct 1958: Toronto, Ontario, Canada). (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - European trip (09 Jun 1959 - 01 Oct 1959: Portugal, Spain, Ialy, Switzerland, France, England, Holland, Germany, Russia). (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Russian trip (30 Jul 1959 - 06 Aug 1959: Russia, USSR). (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Russian trip. Notebook (30 Jul 1959 - 06 Aug 1959: Russia, USSR). (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Russian Trip. Lecture cards (30 Jul 1959 - 06 Aug 1959: Russia, USSR). (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Pierce County Medical Society. Television panel (01 Feb 1960: Seattle, WA). (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Western Regional Conference on Maternal and Perinatal (06 Mar 1960: Chicago, IL). (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Symposium on Hypnosis (11 Mar 1960 - 13 Mar 1960: Palm Springs, CA). (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Pan American Medical Association. 35th Anniversary (02 May 1960 - 11 May 1960: Mexico City, Mexico). (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - St. Louis Society of Aneshesiologists (19 May 1960 - 20 May 1960: St. Louis, MO). (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Reno Surgical Society. Conference (10th: 18 Aug 1960 - 20 Aug 1960: Reno, NV). (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Northwest Anesthesiology Meeting (26 Aug 1960 - 28 Aug 1960: Tacoma, WA). (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - World Congress of Anaesthesiologists (2nd: 05 Sep 1960 - 09 Sep 1960: Toronto, Canada). (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Michigan State Medical Society. Session (27 Sep 1960 - 30 Sep 1960: Detroit, MI). (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting (02 Oct 1960 - 07 Oct 1960: New York, NY). (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Diseases of the Male and Female Pelvis. Symposium (14 Jan 1961: Seattle, WA). (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. Meeting (20 Jan 1961 - 22 Jan 1961: San Francisco, CA). (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Post-Graduate Course in Anesthesia (07 Apr 1961 - 12 Apr 1961: Los Angeles, CA). (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Washington State Hospital Association. Workshop (18 Apr 1961 - 20 Apr 1961: Seattle, WA). (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - American College of Obstetrics and Gynecology. Meeting (24 Apr 1961: Bal Harbour, FL). (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists. Tenth (25 Apr 1961 - 28 Apr 1961: Bal Harbor, FL). (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Resucitation Course (12 May 1961 - 13 May 1961: Seattle, WA). (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - North American Federation of the International Congress of (26th: 14 May 1961 - 18 May 1961: Chicago, IL). (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Western Conference on Anesthesiology (16 May 1961 - 18 May 1961: Portland, OR). (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Faculty Conference on Curriculum (25 May 1961 - 26 May 1961: Pack Forest, La Grande, WA). (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Chelan County Medical Society (05 Jun 1961: Wenatchee, WA). (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - American Society of Medical Technologists. Convention (15 Jun 1961: Seattle, WA). (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - American Medical Association. Section on Anesthesiology (28 Jun 1961 - 30 Jun 1961: New York, NY). (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - International Congress of Medical Electronics (15 Jul 1961: New York, NY). (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Symposium Internacional de Anestesiologia (1st: 01 Aug 1961 - 04 Aug 1961: Bogota, Columbia). (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - University of Washington. School of Medicine. Faculty (18 Oct 1961: Swept Wing, WA). (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting (20 Oct 1961 - 27 Oct 1961: Los Angeles, CA). (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Canadian Anesthetists' Society (16 Feb 1962: Vancouver, BC, Canada). (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - International Anesthesia Research Society. Congress (36th: 18 Mar 1962 - 22 Mar 1962: Bal Harbour, FL). (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Canadian Medical Association. Scientific Session (9th: 04 Apr 1962 - 07 Apr 1962: Harrison Hot Springs, BC, Canada). (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - University of Washington. School of Medicine. Faculty (21 May 1962 - 22 May 1962: Pack Forest, La Grande, WA). (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Post-Graduate Course in Anesthesia (2nd: 18 Jul 1962 - 20 Jul 1962: Seattle, WA). (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Post-Graduate Course in Anesthesia. Evaluation Sheets (18 Jul 1962 - 20 Jul 1962: Seattle, WA). (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Northwest Societies Meeting (25 Jul 1962: Seattle, WA). (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - European Trip (01 Sep 1962 - 26 Oct 1962: Vienna, Austria; Leiden, the Netherlands; Filicudi, Italy; Paris, France; London, England; Montreal, Canada). (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - European Trip Itinerary (01 Sep 1962 - 26 Oct 1962: Vienna, Austria; Leiden, the Netherlands; Filicudi, Italy; Paris, France; London, England; Montreal, Canada). (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Brena. Vienna (01 Sep 1962 - 26 Oct 1962: Vienna, Austria). (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - European Trip (01 Sep 1962 - 26 Oct 1962: Vienna, Austria; Leiden, the Netherlands; Filicudi, Italy; Paris, France; London, England; Montreal, Canada). (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - European Trip, 1962, General (01 Sep 1962 - 26 Oct 1962: Vienna, Austria; Leiden, the Netherlands; Filicudi, Italy; Paris, France; London, England; Montreal, Canada). (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - European Congress of Anesthesiology (1st: 03 Sep 1962 - 09 Sep 1962: Vienna, Austria). (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - International Congress of Physiological Sciences (22nd: 10 Sep 1962 - 17 Sep 1962: Leiden, the Netherlands). (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Washington State Medical Association. Meeting (73rd: 16 Sep 1962 - 19 Sep 1962: Spokane, WA). (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Refresher Course (13th: 20 Oct 1962 - 22 Oct 1962: New York, NY). (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting (20 Oct 1962 - 26 Oct 1962: New York, NY). (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - North Pacific Surgical Association (16 Nov 1962 - 17 Nov 1962: Seattle, WA). (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Congresso Mexicano de Anestesiologia (9th: 18 Nov 1962 - 24 Nov 1962: Mexico City, Mexico). (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - University of Washington. School of Medicine. Faculty (27 Nov 1962: Seattle, WA). (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Postgraduate Assembly in Anesthesiology (16th: 05 Dec 1962 - 08 Dec 1962: New York, NY). (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Bay District Surgical Society. Meeting (23 Jan 1963: Los Angeles, CA). (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - West Coast Anesthesia Residents Program. Meeting (09 Feb 1963 - 10 Feb 1963: San Francisco, CA). (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Los Angeles County Anesthesia Section Postgraduate (16 Feb 1963 - 17 Feb 1963: Los Angeles, CA). (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. Meeting (13 Mar 1963 - 15 Mar 1963: Denver, CO). (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - University of Puget Sound. 75th Anniversary Convocation (17 Mar 1963: Tacoma, WA). (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - International Anesthesia Research Society. Congress (37th: 24 Mar 1963 - 28 Mar 1963: Bal Harbour, FL). (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Western Conference on Anesthesiology (25 Mar 1963 - 29 Mar 1963: Honolulu, Hawaii). (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Japanese Society of Anesthesiology (10th: 01 Apr 1963 - 05 Apr 1963: Osaka, Japan). (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Medical Education for National Defense. Symposium (18 Apr 1963 - 19 Apr 1963: Cape Canaveral, FL). (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - University of Texas. Medical Branch. Tumor Conference (22 Apr 1963: Galveston, TX). (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Symposium on Cancer (12th: 25 Apr 1963: Winston-Salem, NC). (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Pacific Coast Oto-Opthamological Society. Instruction Course (04 May 1963: San Francisco, CA). (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - State Medical Society of Wisconsin. Meeting (122nd: 07 May 1963 - 09 May 1963: Milwaukee, WI). (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Surgical Specialties Group (08 May 1963: Grand Rapids, MI). (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Pulmonary Therapy Seminar (13 May 1963 - 16 May 1963: Seattle, WA). (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Symposium Internazionale sulla Terapia di Blocco della (25 May 1963 - 26 May 1963: Venice, Italy). (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Pack Forest Conference for Leaders of the Medical Profession (01 Jun 1963 - 02 Jun 1963: Pack Forest, La Grange, WA). (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - University of Washington. Commencement (15 Jun 1963: Seattle, WA). (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - American Medical Association. Convention (16 Jun 1963: Atlantic City, NJ). (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Pack Forest Conference on Motivation and the Student of (06 Sep 1963 - 07 Sep 1963: Pack Forest, La Grange, WA). (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Salem, Oregon Surgical Society. Meeting (20 Sep 1963: Salem, Oregon). (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Argentine Congress of Anesthesiology (9th: 06 Oct 1963 - 11 Oct 1963: Buenos Aries, Argentina). (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Jornada Brasileira de Analgesia (1st: 16 Oct 1963: São Paolo, Brazil). (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Sweptwing Inn Conference (16 Oct 1963: Seattle, WA). (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Congress of Pan-Pacific Pain Relief (9th: 05 Nov 1963: Honolulu, HI). (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Postgraduate Assembly in Anesthesiology (17th: 11 Dec 1963 - 13 Dec 1963: New York, NY). (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Postgraduate Seminar in Anesthesiology. The Cardiovascular (05 Jan 1964 - 08 Jan 1964: Miami Beach, FL). (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Puget Sound Academy of Ophthalmology and (17 Jan 1964 - 18 Jan 1964: Seattle, WA). (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Western Society for Clinical Research (29 Jan 1964 - 30 Jan 1964: Carmel, CA). (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - International Anesthesia Research Society. Meeting (15 Mar 1964 - 20 Mar 1964: Las Vegas, NV). (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Spokane Surgical Society. Meeting (29th: 18 Apr 1964: Spokane, WA). (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Venezuelan Society of Anesthesiologists (29 Apr 1964 - 02 May 1964: Caracas, Venezuela). (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Northwest Association of Physical Medicine and (1st: 16 May 1964: Seattle, WA). (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Oregon State Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting (22 May 1964: Salem, OR). (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - American Therapeutic Society. Meeting (65th: 13 Jun 1964 - 17 Jun 1964: Honolulu, HI). (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Albert Einstein College of Medicine (29 Jun 1964 - 03 Jul 1964: New York, NY). (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Northwest Cancer Conference (16 Jul 1964 - 17 Jul 1964: Seattle, WA). (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Conference on Citanest (17 Sep 1964 - 18 Sep 1964: Jequiti-Mar, Guarujá, Brazil). (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - World Congress of Anaesthesiology (3rd: 20 Sep 1964 - 26 Sep 1964: São Paolo, Brazil). (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - World Congress of Anaesthesiology [Planning] (3rd: 20 Sep 1964 - 26 Sep 1964: São Paolo, Brazil). (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Congresso Latino-Americano de Anestesiologia (7th: 29 Sep 1964 - 02 Oct 1964: Montevideo, Uruguay). (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting (10 Oct 1964 - 14 Oct 1964: Bal Harbour, FL). (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - California Academy of General Practice. Meeting (16th: 25 Oct 1964 - 28 Oct 1964: San Francisco, CA). (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - No Name Society. Meeting (12 Nov 1964 - 14 Nov 1964: Seattle, WA). (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Postgraduate Assembly in Anesthesiology. Meeting (18th: 14 Dec 1964 - 16 Dec 1964: New York, NY). (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Committee on (09 Jan 1965 - 10 Jan 1965: San Francisco, CA). (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Executive (23 Jan 1965 - 24 Jan 1965: Chicago, IL). (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Symposium on Cancer Pain (16 Mar 1965 - 24 Mar 1965: Rome, Italy). (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Executive Committee (03 Apr 1965 - 04 Apr 1965: Chicago, IL). (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - National Institute of General Medical Sciences. (08 Apr 1965: New York, NY). (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Family Health Conference (09 Apr 1965: San Francisco, CA). (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Western Conference on Anesthesiology (02 May 1965 - 07 May 1965: Vancouver, BC, Canada). (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Wood Library (14 May 1965: Chicago, IL). (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Lecture at Stanford University (20 May 1965 - 21 May 1965: Palo Alto, CA). (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Budget and Publicity (09 Jun 1965 - 11 Jun 1965: Chicago, IL). (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Executive (19 Jun 1965: New York, NY). (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - American Medical Association. Scientific Council. Meeting (20 Jun 1965 - 24 Jun 1965: New York, NY). (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Committee on (31 Jul 1965: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Committe on (14 Aug 1965: New York, NY). (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Advisory Committee (28 Aug 1965: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Executive Committee (28 Aug 1965 - 29 Aug 1965: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - National Institutes of Health. Meeting (10 Sep 1965 - 11 Sep 1965: Philadelphia, PA). (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Conference on Recruitment and Training for Clinical (10 Sep 1965 - 11 Sep 1965: Philadelphia, PA). (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Utah State Medical Association. Scientific Meeting (70th: 15 Sep 1965 - 17 Sep 1965: Salt Lake City, UT). (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Committee Chairmen (26 Sep 1965: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - American Medical Association. House of Delegates. Meeting (30 Sep 1965 - 03 Oct 1965: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Canadian Anesthetists' Society (07 Oct 1965: Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada). (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - American Medical Association. Forum on Medical Specialties (10 Oct 1965: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - National Academy of Sciences. Autumn Meeting (11 Oct 1965 - 13 Oct 1965: Seattle, WA). (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Academy of Anesthesiology (19 Oct 1965 - 22 Oct 1965: Colorado Springs, CO). (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting (23 Oct 1965 - 27 Oct 1965: Denver, CO). (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - McKesson Memorial Lecture (08 Nov 1965: Toledo, OH). (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - American Medical Association. American Society of (28 Nov 1965 - 04 Dec 1965: Philadelphia, PA). (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Anesthesia Training Program Directors. Meeting (12 Dec 1965: New York, NY). (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - New York Postgraduate Assembly in Anesthesiology (19th: 13 Dec 1965 - 15 Dec 1965: New York, NY). (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Hawaii Trip (17 Dec 1965 - 03 Jan 1966: Honolulu, HI). (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Postgraduate Assembly in Anesthesiology (3rd: 06 Jan 1966 - 09 Jan 1966: Miami Beach, FL). (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - National Academy of Sciences. National Research Council. (22 Jan 1966: Palo Alto, CA). (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Speech Training Program (17 Feb 1966 - 18 Feb 1966: Seattle, WA). (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - National Institutes of Health Site Visit (21 Feb 1966: Detroit, MI). (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - International Anesthesia Research Society. Congress (40th: 27 Feb 1966 - 03 Mar 1966: Bal Harbour, FL). (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - National Institutes of Health Site Visit (03 Mar 1966: Omaha, NE). (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - National Institutes of Health Site Visit (04 Mar 1966: Minneapolis, MN). (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - American Medical Association. Congress on Medical Ethics (1st: 05 Mar 1966 - 06 Mar 1966: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Committee on (06 Mar 1966: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting with Nurse (06 Mar 1966: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - National Institutes of Health. Site Visit (07 Mar 1966: Lexington, KY). (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. Meeting (12 Mar 1966 - 13 Mar 1966: St. Louis, MI). (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Cleveland Clinc Postgraduate Course (16 Mar 1966 - 17 Mar 1966: Cleveland, OH). (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - New Jersey Postgraduate Assembly (7th: 19 Mar 1966: Cherry Hill, NJ). (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Trip to Puerto Rico (20 Mar 1966 - 26 Mar 1966: Santurce, Puerto Rico). (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - West Coast Anesthesia Residents Program. Conference (1st: 30 Apr 1966 - 01 May 1966: Seattle, WA). (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists. (50th: 30 Apr 1966 - 05 May 1966: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Macy Conference (01 May 1966 - 03 May 1966: New York, NY). (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Macy Foundation Conference (01 May 1966 - 03 May 1966: Princeton, NJ). (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Massachusetts Society of Anesthesiologists (06 May 1966: Boston, MA). (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Neurophysiology in Relation to Anesthesia (12 May 1966 - 14 May 1966: Seattle, WA). (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Neurophysiology Conference (13 May 1966 - 14 May 1966: Seattle, WA). (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - University of California. Medical Center. Symposium on Pain. (20 May 1966 - 21 May 1966: San Francisco, CA). (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - University of California. Medical Center. Symposium on Pain. (20 May 1966 - 21 May 1966: San Francisco, CA). (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Meeting with New York anesthesiologists (26 May 1966: Brooklyn, NY). (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Continuation Course in Anesthesiology (01 Jun 1966 - 03 Jun 1966: Minneapolis, MN). (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Departmental Teaching Conference (04 Jun 1966: Seattle, WA). (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - National Conference on Obstetric Anesthesia (10 Jun 1966: Pittsburgh, PA). (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - National Conference on Obstetric Anesthesia (10 Jun 1966: Pittsburgh, PA). (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Budget Meeting (13 Jun 1966 - 14 Jun 1966: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - California Society of Anesthesiologists. Scientific Meeting (2nd: 16 Jun 1966 - 18 Jun 1966: Lake Tahoe, CA). (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Executive (25 Jun 1966: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - American Medical Association. Meeting (26 Jun 1966 - 30 Jun 1966: Chicago, IL). (Box 16, Folder 53)